Ryan J Skelly

Portsmouth, RI & Durham, NH (401) 864-5571 ryan@iatek.com rjs1070@wildcats.unh.edu

I am an outgoing, hardworking, and determined individual. I enjoy learning about and working with many aspects of technology including new gadgets, electric vehicles, computer hardware, and software. I have successfully built three personal computers in my free time. I also have experience coding in HTML, CSS, Python, and JavaScript. I am currently studying Information Technology at the University of New Hampshire.

EDUCATION:

University of New Hampshire, Durham NH - IT Major // • Aug 2019 - PRESENT •

In my studies at UNH, I have completed:

- CS 414 Problems, Algorithms, Programs
- IT 403 Intro to Internet Technologies
- CS 417 Programs to Computer Science
- IT 502 Intermediate Web Design
- CS 515 Data Structures and Introduction to Algorithms

Portsmouth High School, Portsmouth RI // Aug 2015 - May 2019

- Programming with Java
- Microsoft Office Applications
- Technical Drawing (CAD)
- Digital Electronics
- Web Page Development
- AP Computer Science Principles

EXPERIENCE:

Pizza Hollywood, Middletown RI - Delivery Driver & General Asst. // Feb 2019 - PRESENT

15 Point Road Restaurant, Portsmouth RI - Busser // Sep 2017 - Jan 2019

Sisters of St. Dorothy, Bristol RI - Camp Counselor // Jul 2016 - Aug 2016, Jul 2017 - Aug 2017

SKILLS

I am proficient in,

- Microsoft Office
- XML/HTML & CSS
- Python

I also have a good understanding and background in,

- C++
- Java
- JavaScript
- ReactJS
- Using APIs
- Git and Git Repositories
- Terminal Interpreters in Windows/ Linux

CURRENT & PAST PROJECTS

Senior Project Management Web App // https://oxyvnk6vjz.csb.app/

Ryan Skelly Website // ryanskelly.com

AWARDS & RECOGNITION

Portsmouth High School Honor Roll // 2018 - 2019

RI All-State Student-Athlete // 2016 - 2018

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- Software & Coding
- Custom Build Computers
- Outdoors, Skiing & Hiking
- Video Games